Hi, I'm Teo van den Broeke, Editor-in-Chief of Esquire UK.
And I'm Tom Holland, and we're going to be talking today about some things that
make me feel good.
So Tom, golf.
Why golf?
I like golf just because it's incredibly humbling.
Right.
You know, no matter how hard you practice or how often you play, you can
still have days where it feels like you don't or have never played before.
And for me, I have a really overactive brain, which I think has served me
well as a creative.
But sometimes I need things to just help me calm down.
Have you ever shot a hole in one?
I have done.
I've had two hole in ones.
Really?
The first one, unfortunately, I was by myself.
Right.
So no one believes me, which is really unfortunate.
And then the second one, I was actually playing in a match against a scratch
golfer.
Okay.
And I went against his judgment on what club to hit.
Right.
And it went in.
That's quite amazing.
I mean, people kind of run for their mental health, right?
Because it's easy.
You can throw on some trainers, go out into the...
Like, to play golf for your mental health, you need a...
I was going to say a pitch.
You can say that.
A course.
You need a course.
You need all of the kit and everything.
How often do you find yourself able to play?
I try and play as much as I can if I'm not working and I
have nothing to do I really do play every day right that's that's quite a
commitment I wouldn't say golf is good for my mental health right because I'm quite
a hothead and I can get quite angry on the golf course making me nervous
about you showing yeah yeah and I am I can get really angry but no
I like I play with my friends I have a great group of guys that
I've played with for you know 10 years plus right and um some of them
are much better than me some of them are sort of the same level as
me and then there's a couple guys you know exactly who i'm talking about who
are f***ing s*** um and no i love it i absolutely love it okay let
me see what you're working with tell me about me okay here we go it's
the 18th hole right so am i aiming for a hole in yes yeah yeah
okay last putt to win the masters which is next weekend already looking a bit
left yeah there you go okay try and try and close your hips a little
bit so like there you go that's a better that's a better point now I've
touched it does that mean it doesn't count that's okay you see how your club
is closed yeah you let go of it okay that's squarer to your stance there
you go that should be a better shot okay and then I'm looking at the
hole just trying to aim up just look at the ball okay and don't even
look at where it goes oh really yeah that feels counterintuitive that's better oh you
hit it just a little softer that'll go in okay i'm enjoying these tips though
right so that's better close the face a little bit now you've overcompensated there you
go okay and a little softer and it'll go in okay i dread to think
about this stance is looking on camera no you look you look a little bit
like you're taking a poo okay you're okay three two one come Come on, Teo.
That's good.
Yes!
Tom.
There we go.
Didn't need any teaching.
Lessons for feeling good and playing golf.
Thank you for that.
I think that was kind of a perfect ending to the video.
That's actually quite amazing.
What a dream.
You don't even need to see me hit it now.
I don't want to after you've drained it.
No, okay, but you trained me.
That's good.
That's a point.
That was great.
You were a good listener.
You took the direction on really nicely.
Oh, I appreciate that.
Okay, so you're not doing the poo stance.
I'm not as tall as you, though.
There you go.
Sir.
If I miss all of these, I'm going to get crucified.
Very good.
There we go.
I noticed your follow through.
That was good.
Thank you.
But you keep going.
Yeah, it's just like you kind of want to point at the target.
So wherever the club ends up, like if I put the club, if I followed
through to here.
It's going to go here.
The chances are is the club will go left.
Aha.
So you kind of want to always point at the target.
It looks like Tom and I got the same score.
Well, I missed that one on purpose.
Do you have any tap dancing experience?
No.
Okay.
Tap dancing is all about being able to transfer your weight from foot to foot.
Right, so you want to be able to kind of...
Like a footballer.
Like a footballer or a boxer.
If you were boxing, you'd want to be able to change your weight.
So the first thing you're going to do is stamp.
And then you're going to pull your toe back.
That's the first step.
Okay, so...
No, no, no.
So stamp, pull your toes up.
That's it.
Got it.
Okay, so the next thing is...
Oh my God.
No, I'm joking, I'm joking, I'm joking.
This is hard.
Stamp, heel, click, pop.
No.
Stamp.
God, I sound like one of my teachers already.
No, do it again.
Stamp, kick, hop, step.
You're very patient, Tom.
I got it.
I think we do this once more and then we stop because I'm not going
to get it.
Okay.
Hop.
Tell me about movement.
It's really important.
Why is movement important to you?
I think because I've always played characters that have a physicality as a big part
of telling that story.
When you play Spider-Man and you put a mask on, you don't have your face
to be able to convey to the audience what's going on.
So you have to find a way to physically kind of tell that story.
And sometimes with Spider-Man it can be as simple as cocking the head, usually tells
the people that he's confused, you know, surprise is just like lifting your shoulders up
a little bit.
Right.
And doing that now in regular clothes feels really hammy.
But when you do it in the suit, it really translates really well.
So it's almost like mine.
It's a little bit like mine.
Right.
You were saying there's something about like that I have perfect turnout.
That is actually incredible to be fair.
Thanks.
Something I've done right.
Can you plié from there?
How do we plié?
The plié is just down.
And then if you were going to grand plié, you would go all the way
down.
Okay, I'll move this.
All these shorts are going to rip.
I like that.
But you can pick your heels up off the floor with a grand plié.
Okay.
There you go.
Yeah, that looks really good.
That's quite Spider-Man.
Yeah, you just take it one step further and go down.
so tom tell me skincare skincare routines do you have one uh yes and no
if i'm working i have an amazing makeup artist who takes fantastic care of my
skin and if i'm not working you know just a nice little splash of water
in the morning is kind of and i do moisturize and wear SPF but that's
kind of about it is there any specific moisturizer you go for yes I wouldn't
be able to tell you the name of it though and I don't buy it
my my lady is in charge of buying all of those creams and stuff I
just one of the benefits is that I steal all of her stuff I was
gonna say so they're they're not your specific creams that you're using and they're probably
far more expensive than I think they are you know I'm probably putting far too
much moisturizer on uh than I should be.
Other than tap and golf is there anything in your daily routine you do to
make sure you can take care of yourself?
Probably just daily exercise to be honest.
I've been very bad recently I've been traveling a lot so my exercise has taken
a hit but if I'm at home and I have a good schedule going I'll
exercise every day without fail.
What does that look like?
Depends on what I'm doing you know if I'm making a movie then I'm probably
doing like more fitness based stuff to try and make sure I can keep my
energy up throughout the day.
If I'm prepping for a movie, for a Spider-Man or the Odyssey, it's all about
trying to put on as much weight as possible.
So it kind of varies from day to day, really.
What are the things in your life that help keep you grounded?
Definitely my family and my friends.
You know, I'm very lucky to have a group of friends that will always be
incredibly honest and are not yes people.
That has been something for me that has really, really helped me, especially as my
life changed as quickly as it did.
But yeah, I'd say my friends and my family.
If you could go back and give your younger self one piece of advice, what
would it be?
To be perfectly honest with you, I am so happy with where I'm at in
my life right now.
I probably wouldn't change anything.
You know, like I've made mistakes and and and all that sort of stuff.
But I've learned from all of them.
So I think I probably would maybe tell myself to take more holidays as a
younger person, maybe go traveling.
Actually, my cousin is just about to go traveling through Asia.
And I really wish when I was sort of 17, 18, that I had done
something like that, like thrown a backpack on and traveled somewhere.
So maybe maybe that's what I would have told myself.
Is there one destination you've not been to that you'd really kind of make a
beeline for?
I mean, I've been to Japan a bunch of times for work, but never for
pleasure.
and I would love to go and explore Japan.
Quickfire round.
Morning cleanse or water rinse?
Water rinse.
Same daily routine or switch it up?
I probably would have to say switch it up only because I'm terrible at keeping
to a routine.
SPF only on sunny days or every single day?
Every day SPF.
That sounds like a self-care routine to me.
Yeah, but that's very simple.
That's like moisturizer and sun cream rolled into one.
Got it.
Serum or moisturizer?
I don't know the difference.
lifting weights or cardio i prefer to lift weights but cardio is better for you
early bird or night owl i would say i'm more of a night owl i
am pretty good at getting up at a good time but i would rather i
would much rather stay in bed what's a what's an average bedtime average bedtime i
think about 11 maybe average wake-up time seven that's pretty strict to that yoga or
run yoga Chicken salad or Big Mac?
I actually don't like Big Mac.
That's not what I order from McDonald's.
I would rather a salad.
Hot or cold shower?
A hot shower.
Sauna or steam?
Sauna.
Wimbledon or World Cup?
What, like, would I like to win either of them?
Yeah.
I mean, it'd have to be the World Cup.
Really?
Yeah, because, you know, to play as a team would be really special.
But Wimbledon is so special.
and maybe one of the greatest sporting events of all time.
But then so is the World Cup.
I'd have to say, especially because the World Cup is this year, I'm going to
put it out there and say the World Cup.
Thank you, Tom.
Thank you.
Okay.
Oh, that's the microphone.